Brooke Mortensen

Front End Web Developer

801.556.6803



brookemorte@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/brookemortensen



github.com/brookemo



profile

Front End Web Developer able to build a sophisticated website that not only looks great but works great too. Loves learning new technologies, and quick to pick up on them. Understands the importance of User Experience. Loves simple and clean work.

skills

React.js, Node.js, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Handlebars, MySQL, MongoDB, Github, Firebase, Bootstrap, Materialize, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, and the command line.

education

FULL STACK BOOTCAMP

University of Utah January 2018 - July 2018 An intensive 24-week long bootcamp dedicated to building web applications from start to finish.

past experience

Wordpress Editor @ Single Dad Laughing January 2018 - March 2018

Concierge @ The Grand America Hotel October 2015 - January 2018

applications built

S K 8

Front End Developer

A web application that allows users to create a profile and share skating tricks with other skaters in their area.

I used Javascript, JSON, jQuery, AJAX calls, HTML, CSS, Materialize, the Geolocation API and the Google Maps APIs.

https://stark-savannah-69359.herokuapp.com/

AVENGERS ASSEMBLER

Front End Developer

A web application that connects users to information regarding their favorite Avengers Characters.

I worked on a team, and was responsible for the front end development of the character pages., and all mobile responsiveness. Using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, and the IMBD/OMBD API.

https://clickomat.github.io/goonies/

MAMMA MIA MEMORY GAME

Full Stack Developer

A simple memory game built with React.js where the player can try to remember what card they clicked.

I used React.js, node.js, HTML, CSS, Javascript, and jQuery.

https://brookemo.github.io/clickygame/